#### COMPETENCIES

Human centered design methodology Design thinking User research methods Agile methodology Storytelling Visual design Prototyping HTML5 CSS3 Vuejs Git

#### TOOLS

Paper, pen, sticky notes Whiteboard Figma, Adobe XD etc Jira, Confluence

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Avid learner Attentive to details Problem solver Excellent communicator Organised Team player Goal oriented

# CONTACT

Phone: +49 15210186641 email: busayomioyewole@gmailcom

# **BUSAYO OYEWOLE**

# USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a human-centered designer with background in psychology and frontend development. I've had experience designing interactive products such as a fintech AI solution and a B2B e-commerce service. I'm currently rounding up my masters degree in Usability Engineering and set to graduate in November 2019

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER Siegwerk AG | Feb 2019 - Present Responsibilities include:

- Working closely with product owner on vision for product
- Employing the HCD process and methods to solve business problems
- Refining product based on new business requirements & user insights
- Visual design of user interface
- Communicating design solutions to developers and stakeholders
- Facilitating design sprint and workshops

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

FLAQSHIP GmbH | April 2018 - August 2018 Responsibilities included:

- Implementing UI designs using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript
- Testing and fixing websites for usability, functionality, crossbrowser compatibility and responsive issues
- Collaborating with other stakeholders to ensure userfacing features are well implemented

### INTERACTION DESIGNER

Kudi Inc | June 2016 - September 2017 Responsibilties included:

- Conducting user and market research
- Crafting out bot-human experience for financial use cases
- UX writing of bot replies to suit designed contexts
- Conducting usability tests
- Working closely with developers and stakeholders to bring product to life

# **EDUCATION**

MSC. USABILITY ENGINEERING

Rhine-waal university of applied sciences | 2017 - 2019 (set to graduate in November 2019)

MSC. PSYCHOLOGY

Obafemi Awolowo University | 2010 -2015 Upper Second-Class Honours